import { Quiz } from "../types/Quiz";

export const quizes1: Array<Quiz> = [
  {
    question: "Tom asked his dad for ___ to go to the party.",
    answers: ["discovery", "experiments", "permission"],
    correctAnswer: "permission",
  },
  {
    question: "___ can cause diseases.",
    answers: ["Bacteria", "Mold", "Experiments"],
    correctAnswer: "Bacteria",
  },
  {
    question: "This book has a beautiful ___ on the cover.",
    answers: ["capture", "illustration", "president"],
    correctAnswer: "illustration",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If you leave food outside the fridge for a long time, ___ can grow on it.",
    answers: ["president", "bacteria", "mold"],
    correctAnswer: "mold",
  },
  {
    question: "Jane made a surprising ___.",
    answers: ["discovery", "capture", "experiments"],
    correctAnswer: "discovery",
  },
  {
    question: "Mr. Brown is the ___ of the bank.",
    answers: ["bacteria", "Evolution", "president"],
    correctAnswer: "president",
  },
  {
    question: "Scientists conduct ___ to test their theories.",
    answers: ["discovery", "experiments", "permission"],
    correctAnswer: "experiment",
  },
  {
    question: "Jack is very ___. He never cleans his room.",
    answers: ["capture", "sloppy", "president"],
    correctAnswer: "sloppy",
  },
  {
    question: "Darwin is famous for his Theory of ___.",
    answers: ["mold", "president", "Evolution"],
    correctAnswer: "Evolution",
  },
  {
    question: "The whole town tried to ___ the escaped bear.",
    answers: ["discovery", "experiments", "capture"],
    correctAnswer: "capture",
  },
];

export const quizes2: Array<Quiz> = [
  {
    question: "A: ...\nB: He's an air traffic controller",
    answers: [
      "What does your dad do for a living?",
      "Is it full-time?",
      "Is the pay good?",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "What does your dad do for a living?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A: ...\nB: He directs airplanes and warns them of any danger in the sky.",
    answers: [
      "What does your dad do for a living?",
      "Does he like it?",
      "What does that involve?",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "What does that involve?",
  },
  {
    question: "A: ...\nB: Yes, he really loves his job.",
    answers: ["Is the pay good?", "Does he like it?", "Is it full time?"],
    correctAnswer: "Does he like it?",
  },
  {
    question: "A: ...\nB: Yes, but he works different shifts",
    answers: ["Is the pay good?", "Is it full time?", "Does he like it?"],
    correctAnswer: "Is it full time?",
  },
  {
    question: "A: ...\nB: Yes, he earns a lot of money.",
    answers: ["Is it full-time?", "Does he like it?", "Is the pay good?"],
    correctAnswer: "Is the pay good?",
  },
];
